steelersdepot.com 2012-12-20

# Privacy Policy | Steelers Depot

**Privacy Policy for http://www.steelersdepot.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin**(AT)**steelersdepot.com.

Steelers Depot knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers Steelers Depot’s treatment of personal information that Steelers Depot gathers when you are on the Steelers Depot website and when you use Steelers Depot services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Steelers Depot does not own or control, or to individuals that Steelers Depot does not employ or manage.

Information Collected by Steelers Depot

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our Steelers Depot users:

1\. Information You Provide to Us:

We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

2\. Automatic Information:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Steelers Depot and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain “traffic data” on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, Steelers Depot cookie information, and the page you requested. Steelers Depot uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.

Steelers Depot may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed.

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Steelers Depot will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

3\. E-mail Communications:

Steelers Depot is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the “Sharing Your Information” section below. Steelers Depot may send out e-mails with Steelers Depot-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions.

4\. Cookies:

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Steelers Depot cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.

The “help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of Steelers Depot’s coolest features.

Steelers Depot’s advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that makes it possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads. If you would prefer to opt-out of this standard practice, please visit our advertising partner Platform-A’s privacy policy and opt-out page.

5\. Sharing Your Information:

Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.

6\. Steelers Depot Personnel:

Steelers Depot personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of Steelers Depot business.

7\. Business Transfers:

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Steelers Depot, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.

8\. Protection of Steelers Depot and Others:

We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Steelers Depot, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

9\. Syndication:

Steelers Depot allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the Steelers Depot website.

10\. With Your Consent:

Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.

11\. Children Under 18 Years of Age:

You must be 13 years and older to register to use the Steelers Depot website. As a result, Steelers Depot does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that Steelers Depot has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents’ permission before using Steelers Depot or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.

12\. Changes to this Privacy Policy:

Steelers Depot may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Steelers Depot website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

13\. Conditions of Use:

If you decide to visit Steelers Depot website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.

14\. Effective Date of this Privacy Policy:

This Privacy Policy is effective as of July 21, 2010 and last updated July 21, 2010.

#### Incoming search terms for the article:

  * steelers depot rss
  * authorized steelers fan shop
  * interent traffic to steelers depot
  * special needs children at steeler training camp
  * steelers and its types
  * steelers browser
  * www the steelers depot com

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
